A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33
  - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1981 (Bulk: 1977-1981); 1977-1981; 25
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Employees - Marshack, Megan (Box 549, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death (Box 549, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Clippings (Box 549, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - General Correspondence (Box 549, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - A (Box 550, Folder 1-7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - BA-BL (Box 551, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - BM-BZ (Box 552, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - CA-CI (Box 553, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - CJ-CZ (Box 554, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - DA-DO (Box 555, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - DP-FL (Box 556, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - FM-GH (Box 557, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - GI-HAM (Box 558, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - HAN-HOP (Box 559, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - HOR-JZ (Box 560, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - K (Box 561, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - L-LO (Box 562, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - LO-MB (Box 563, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - MCA-MK (Box 564, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - ML-N (Box 565, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - N-PA (Box 566, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - PB-PZ (Box 567, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - Q-RN (Box 568, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - RO-SB (Box 569, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - SC-SIR (Box 570, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - SIS-SZ (Box 571, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - T-V (Box 572, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - V-WN (Box 573, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Condolences - WO-Z (Box 574, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Memorial Service (Box 574, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Memorial Service - Attendees (Box 575, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Memorial Service - Attendees - Foreign Diplomats (Box 575, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Memorial Service - Invitation Lists (Box 575, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Memorial Service - Invitees, Requests (Box 575, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Memorial Service - Invitees, Requests (Box 576, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Confidential material
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Estate (Box 576, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Estate - Executor's Meetings (Box 576, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Press Releases (Box 577, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Death - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Letters of Appreciation (Box 577, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Finances (Box 577, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Furnishings (Box 577, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Gifts (Box 577, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Giving Program (Box 577, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection (Box 577, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - A-B (Box 577, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - C-Z (Box 578, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Articles (Box 579, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Bleecker, Samuel (Box 579, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Books - Masterpieces of the 20th Century (Box 579, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Books - Masterpieces of Primitive Art (Box 579, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue (Box 579, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue - Requests - A-G (Box 580, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue - Requests - H-N (Box 581, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Catalogue - Requests - O-Z (Box 582, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Consultants (Box 582, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Finances (Box 582, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - New Talent Club (Box 583, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Promotion (Box 583, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Radio-TV (Box 583, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Sale (Box 583, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Collection - Sale - Trenchfield Management Services Ltd. (Box 583, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Nelson Rockefeller Publications, Inc. (Box 583, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam Corp. (Box 583, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam NV - Correspondence (Box 583, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam NV - Articles of Incorporation (Box 583, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Corporate Record File (Box 583, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Corporate Structure (Box 583, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam NV - Finances (Box 584, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Finances, 1977 (Box 584, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Kuwait Agreement (Box 584, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Lease (Box 584, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam NV - List of Participants (Box 584, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Meetings-Minutes (Box 584, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam NV - Minutes of Management Meetings-Voting Agreement-Non Voting Agreement (Box 584, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Newsclips (Box 584, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Notes (Box 584, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Investments - Sarabam - Proposals (Box 584, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations - A-R (Box 585, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations - S-Z (Box 586, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. -Invitations to Speak - A-E (Box 586, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations to Speak - F-N (Box 587, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations to Speak - O-Z (Box 588, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Jewelry (Box 589, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Kissinger, Henry (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 589, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Memorials (Box 589, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Personal Services (Box 589, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Photos - A-N (Box 589, Folder 5-6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Photos - N-Z (Box 590, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Politics (Box 590, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS (Box 590, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro (Box 590, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Photographs - Hacienda and Chapel (Box 590, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Sale (Box 590, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - A-H (Box 590, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - I-Z (Box 591, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Monte Sacro - Universidad Metropolitana (Box 591, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Michigan Hill (Box 591, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Personal (Box 592, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Legal (Box 592, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - NARFARMS - Legal (Box 592, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - 812 Fifth Avenue (Box 592, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 592, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - A-P (Box 592, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - Q-Z (Box 593, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 593, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Seal Harbor - Sale (Box 593, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Index of Correspondence (Box 593, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas (Box 593, Folder 5-6, Box 594, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Construction (Box 594, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Blueprints and Maps (Box 594, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Durham, Albert (Beto) (Box 595, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - East, Alice (Mrs. T.T.) Robert Thomas (Box 595, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Equipment (Box 595, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Finances (Box 595, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Furnishings (Box 595, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Game Preserve (Box 595, Folder 7, Box 596, Folder 1-4, Box 597, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Legal (Box 597, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Notes (Box 597, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Ogden, Peter K. (Roberts and Roberts) - Correspondence and Expenses (Box 597, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Photos-Snapshots (Box 598, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Port Mansfield Airport Proposal (Box 598, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Willacy County Navigation District Real Estate Potential (Box 598, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Utilities (Box 598, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - Texas - Iturria, Frank (Box 599, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - 2500 Foxhall Road (Box 599, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Property - 2500 Foxhall Road - Sale (Box 599, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Purchases (Box 600, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Radio-TV (Box 600, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Schedules (Box 600, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Staff (Box 600, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Smith. Bert (Box 601, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips (Box 601, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips, France-Turkey, Saudi Arabia, Kuwait, Pakistan, Afghanistan, India and Switzerland, 1978 April-May (Box 601, Folder 3-4, Box 602, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - France-Iran, 1977 October (Box 602, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trips - Middle East, 1977 (Box 602, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - U.S. Government - Coordination of Inter-American Affairs (Box 602, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - U.S. Government - President's Advisory Committee on Government Organization (Box 602, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 603, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Works of Art - Sotheby Park Bernet (Box 603, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - A-O (Box 604, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - P-Z (Box 605, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Articles (Box 605, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 605, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Gifts (Box 605, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Invitations (Box 605, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Invitations to Speak (Box 605, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Trips (Box 605, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Trips - Europe 1979 (Box 606, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Works of Art (Box 606, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Mary Clark (Box 606, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Richard G. (Box 606, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Richard G. - Dune Fund (Box 606, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Rodman C. (Box 606, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Rodman C. (Mrs.) Barbara (Box 606, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Mrs.) Happy - Trips with Children (Box 607, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, Jr. (Box 607, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, Jr. - Trusts - Knickerbocker Club (Box 607, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Peter C. (Box 607, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Rebecca Anderson (Box 607, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Sandra (Box 607, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Sandra - Community Fund No. 205 (Box 607, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Steven C. (Box 607, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Steven C. (Mrs.) Dori (Box 608, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Stephen C. - Giving Program (Box 607, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Steven C., Jr. (Box 608, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Stuart A. (Box 608, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trusts (Box 608, Folder 4)
    - Simpson, Abby Rockefeller (Box 608, Folder 5)
    - Simpson, William K. (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Trust (Box 608, Folder 6)
    - Spencer, David Hooker (Box 608, Folder 7)
    - Strawbridge, Geodfrey T. (Box 608, Folder 8)
    - Strawbridge, Michael R. (Box 608, Folder 9)
    - Strawbridge, Sabrina (Box 608, Folder 10)
    - Waletzky, Jeremy P. (Dr. and Mrs.) Lucy R. Hamlin - The Genesis Fund (Box 608, Folder 11-12)
    - Weber, Warren T. (Mr. and Mrs.) - Marion F. Rockefeller (Box 608, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Estate - A-Z (Box 609, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Estate - Finances (Box 610, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Estate - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust (Box 610, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 611, Folder 1)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust - Grants (Box 611, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Winrock Farms, Inc. (Box 611, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Mrs. (Jeannette) (Box 611, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Wintrhop Paul (Box 611, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Winrock International (Box 612, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul - Winrock Farms (Box 612, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul (Mrs.) Deborah Sage (Box 612, Folder 3)
    - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton (Box 612, Folder 4)
    - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Charitable Income Trust (Box 612, Folder 5)
    - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Charitable Income Trust - A-Z (Box 612, Folder 6-8)
    - Simpson, William Kelly (Mr. and Mrs.) Marilyn Milton - Charitable Income Trust - University of Pennsylvania School of Veterinary (Box 613, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1977-1981; 26
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A (Box 613, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - B-C (Box 614, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - D-I (Box 615, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - J-N (Box 616, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - N-W (Box 617, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - W-Z (Box 618, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 618, Folder 3-4)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 618, Folder 5)
    - Contributions (Box 619, Folder 1)
    - Creel Committee (Box 619, Folder 3)
    - Corporate Philanthropy (Box 619, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Agency Task Force (Box 619, Folder 4, Box 620, Folder 1-2)
    - Finances (Box 620, Folder 3, Box 621, Folder 1-3, Box 622, Folder 1)
    - Grants (Box 622, Folder 2)
    - Grants - A-Z (Box 622, Folder 3)
    - International Program (Box 622, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Center for Political Alternatives (Box 622, Folder 5)
    - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation (Box 623, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) (Box 623, Folder 2-4)
    - Annual Meetings (Box 624, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1981 (Box 624, Folder 3, Box 625, Folder 1-3)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1980 (Box 626, Folder 1-5, Box 627, Folder 1)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1979 (Box 627, Folder 2-3, Box 628, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1978 (Box 628, Folder 3-5, Box 629, Folder 1-3, Box 630)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1977 (Box 631, Folder 1-5, Box 632, Folder 1-2)
    - National Program (Box 632, Folder 3)
    - National Resources Defense Council (Box 633, Folder 1)
    - New York City Program (Box 633, Folder 2)
    - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine (NYCOM) (Box 633, Folder 3-4, Box 634, Folder 1-2)
    - New York Zoological Society - Animal Kingdom Fund (Box 634, Folder 3)
    - Planning and Review Committee (Box 634, Folder 4, Box 635, Folder 1)
    - Phoenix House and Foundation, Inc. (Box 635, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Family (Box 635, Folder 3)
    - Solar Energy (Box 635, Folder 4)
    - Special Reports (Box 635, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1977-1981; 27
    - Rockefeller Family Fund - A-Z (Box 637, Folder 1-4)
    - Annual Reports (Box 638, Folder 1-3)
    - Annual Report 1980 (Box 638, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report 1979 (Box 638, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report 1978 (Box 638, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report 1977 (Box 638, Folder 7, Box 639, Folder 1-2)
    - Contributions (Box 636, Folder 5)
    - Finances (Box 636, Folder 6)
    - Grants (Box 639, Folder 3)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1978-1979 (Box 639, Folder 4)
    - Minutes-Meetings 1977 (Box 639, Folder 5, Box 640, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller Family Office, 1977-1981; 28
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - General (Box 636, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - Board of Directors (Box 636, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates - Board of Managers (Box 636, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Family Office - A-Z (Box 636, Folder 7)
    - 5600 Inc. (Box 636, Folder 8)
    - Matching Gifts (Box 636, Folder 9)
    - Office Operations (Box 641, Folder 1)
    - Personal Assistance Cases (Box 641, Folder 2)
    - Management (Box 641, Folder 3)
    - Office Directories (Box 641, Folder 4)
    - Task Force (Box 641, Folder 5)
    - Public Affairs - A-R (Box 640, Folder 3-4)
    - Public Affairs - S-Z (Box 642, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Peter Beter (Box 642, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs - Charles A. Lindbergh (Box 642, Folder 3-4, Box 643, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Alvin Moscow Material (Box 643, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs - Alvin Moscow Manuscript - Part I (Box 643, Folder 3-4)
    - Public Affairs - Alvin Moscow Manuscript - Part II (Box 644, Folder 1-2)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - A, C (Box 644, Folder 4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - C-G (Box 645, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - H-L (Box 646, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - M-R (Box 647, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - S-W (Box 648, Folder 1-5)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - W-Z (Box 649, Folder 1-2)
    - Public Affairs - JDR Jr. Credo (Box 649, Folder 3)
    - Public Affairs - Rockefeller Family News Summary, 1977-1980 (Box 649, Folder 4-7)
    - Public Affairs - Rockefeller Family News Summary, 1981 (Box 650, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977-1981; 29
    - Rockefeller Foundation - A-J (Box 650, Folder 2-4)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - K-Z (Box 651, Folder 1-4)
    - Minutes-Meetings, 1977 (Box 652, Folder 1-2)
    - Printed Matter (Box 652, Folder 3)
    - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Youth Award (Box 652, Folder 4)
    - Villa Bellagio Conference Study Center (Box 653, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University, 1977-1981; 30
    - Rockefeller University - A-Z (Box 653, Folder 2-3)
    - Articles (Box 654, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 654, Folder 2)
    - Contributions (Box 654, Folder 3)
    - Council (Box 654, Folder 4)
    - Council - A-Z (Box 654, Folder 5)
    - Council - Meetings-Minutes (Box 654, Folder 6)
    - Council - David Rockefeller (Box 666, Folder 3)
    - Development Committee (Box 654, Folder 7)
    - Finances (Box 655, Folder 1)
    - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 655, Folder 2-4)
    - Fund Raising - RBF (Box 656, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller University - Minutes-Meetings (Box 656, Folder 3)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 656, Folder 4)
    - Fairfield Osborn Memorial (Box 656, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material (Box 656, Folder 6)
    - Releases (Box 657, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 657, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Contributions (Box 657, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Hillcrest Conference, 1981 October 9-10 (Box 657, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Leonard Outhwaite (Box 657, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - David Rockefeller material (Box 657, Folder 7, Box 658, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Printed Matter (Box 658, Folder 2)
    - Sutton House Associates (City Block) (Box 658, Folder 3)
    - Works of Art (Box 658, Folder 4)
  - S, 1977-1981; 31
    - S - Miscellaneous - S-SD (Box 658, Folder 5)
    - S - Miscellaneous - SE-SZ (Box 659, Folder 1-2)
    - Science - A-M (Box 659, Folder 3)
    - Science - N-Z (Box 660, Folder 1)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest (Box 660, Folder 2)
    - Science - Federation of American Scientist Fund (Box 660, Folder 3)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute (Box 660, Folder 4)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute - Printed Matter (Box 661, Folder 1)
    - Science - Institute of Society, Ethics and The Life Sciences (Box 661, Folder 2)
    - Science - Union of Concerned Scientists (Box 661, Folder 3)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-Z (Box 662, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - A-Z (Box 662, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Board of Trustees (Box 662, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Contributions (Box 662, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Finances (Box 662, Folder 5, Box 663, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Croton Associates (Box 663, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Minutes-Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 663, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Minutes-Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 664, Folder 1-5)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Printed Material and Clippings (Box 665, Folder 1)
  - T-W, 1977-1981; 32
    - T - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 2-3)
    - U - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 4)
    - V - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 5)
    - W - Miscellaneous (Box 665, Folder 6, Box 666, Folder 1)
    - Westchester Organizations - A-Z (Box 666, Folder 2)
  - Welfare, 1977-1981; 33
    - Welfare - A-N (Box 667, Folder 1-3)
    - Welfare - O-Z (Box 668, Folder 1)